(Penny:)Are we talking one-night stand
or do we wanna get him into a relationship?
(Amy:)Let's get him laid.
(Raj:)Stop it, you're ruining girls' night.
(Penny:)Raj, you're a great guy, you're in a bar
full of single women. Let us help you.
(Bernadette:)You're a real catch.
(Bernadette:)You're shy, but that doesn't mean
you shouldn't have someone in your life.
(Raj:)That's sweet of you,
but what can you do to help?
(Bernadette:)We'll nose around, see if we can find
a nice girl and then introduce you.
Okay. A couple of things.
(Raj:)Don't tell them I come from money,
I want them to love me for me.
(Raj:)They must be insanely hot.
Like nines or 10s.
Nines or 10s?
(Raj:)Okay, an eight is acceptable if she's willing
to bring another eight to the hot tub.
(Bernadette:)You'll take any woman
who'll have you, right?
(Raj:)In a New Delhi minute.
(Stuart:)I don't remember you buying these
miniatures in my store.